Carra, Lawrence, Papers 1931-1997
Carnegie Mellon University
Four boxes (Boxes 1-4); 4 linear feet
Carnegie Mellon University Archives, Hunt Library, 5000 Forbes Avenue, Pittsburgh, PA
Carra, Lawrence, 1909-2006; Carnegie Mellon University
Shakespeare, William, 1564-1616--Dramatic works; College and school drama, American--Pennsylvania--Pittsburgh; College and school drama, American--Texas--Austin; College and school drama, American--Illinois--Evanston; Universities and colleges--Faculty; Commedia dell'arte; Television plays; Theater--Production and direction; Theater, Municipal--Pennsylvania--Pittsburgh; Drama festivals--Great Lakes; Acting teachers; Musical theater
Biographical Sketch
Lawrence (Larry) Carra was a professor of the Carnegie Mellon University drama department for 31 years, from 1946-1977. He directed over 350 plays in Texas, Boston, New Jersey, Chicago, and Pittsburgh. He is also the co-author of the definitive text on directing, Fundamentals of Play Directing, which is now in its fifth edition. At Carnegie Mellon he was appointed the Chairman of the General Committee on Television in 1957 where he worked closely with WQED and KDKA to produced educational programming about theater. He directed a summer theater program at CMU from 1975-1980. He produced local music festivals and participated in many different types of drama outreach. He helped establish the Pittsburgh Music Tent in 1958-1959, and also directed plays for the Civic Light Opera from 1959-1963. In addition to his stage activities, Carra also worked in television production.
In retirement, Mr. Carra lectured at NYU, UCLA, and USC, while also appearing as a guest director occasionally. He also served as a consultant for the Ice Capades and Norman Lear Productions. Carra's former students include William Ball (American Conservatory Theatre, San Francisco), Mel Shapiro (Broadway producer), John Tebelak (author of 'Godspell'), Sada Thompson ('Family'), Jack Klugman ('Quincy' and 'Odd Couple'), and Ken Welch (music and lyrics for 'Roots').
Scope and Content Note
The Lawrence Carra Papers are housed in four archival boxes and arranged into six series. Series have been designated for biographical information, project files, reference files, stage productions, television and radio productions, and oversized materials. Generally, these papers include informal and business correspondence, newspaper clippings, playbills, scripts, production notes, and set designs. The majority of the collection is information about the vast number of stage and television productions directed by Mr. Carra. These subject folders can include playbills, scripts, attendance sheets, rehearsal schedules and other production notes. The amount of information about each production varies widely. The collection contains little information about his personal life, aside from brief mentions in scattered correspondence throughout the collection. There is little information about the operation of the broader Carnegie Mellon University drama department in the collection.
Provenance
These materials were received in one accession as a gift from Mr. Larry Carra, Jr.
Restrictions
None.
Separations
A half foot of photographs have been separately arranged and described as the Carra, Lawrence, Photographs collection. Also, oversized materials in this collection have been separated from their original folders and stored together for preservation reasons. They are stored in the second floor map case in drawer 8. A list of materials can be found in series six.
Container List
- Biographical information (1936-1997), The biographical information about Lawrence Carra is housed in one folder. It contains newspaper and magazine articles about his work in Chicago, Texas, New Jersey, Ohio, and Pittsburgh. Some of the articles are written by him and one article is a transcript of an interview held in 1976. This folder also contains a published history of the CMU drama department which describes his time as the head of the department. His obituary from the Pittsburgh Post-Gazette was added to this file.
  - Biographical information1936-1997 (Folder 1)
- Project files (1936-1995), The project files are housed in 15 folders arranged alphabetically by the folder title provided by the creator. They contain materials on various activities in which Mr. Carra was active (as a director, lecturer, or consultant) and contain mostly articles, correspondence, and various project reports or playbills. These activity files span almost 60 years and provide the majority of the documentation of his activities in retirement. Of particular interest are the materials about his tenure as chairman of the general television committee at CMU in 1957, which provide some insight into the intentions and procedures of CMU's involvement with WQED and KDKA.
  - Carnegie Institute of Technology1950-1957 (Folder 2)
  - Civic Light Opera1961-1995 (Folder 3)
  - Cochese College Teachers' Seminar1983-1988 (Folder 4)
  - Curtain Club, University of Texas Experimental Theater1941-1945 (Folder 5)
  - Great Lakes Shakespeare Festival1966-1991 (Folder 6)
  - Ice Capades1965 (Folder 7)
  - Mill Playhouse1953-1956 (Folder 8)
  - New Haven Drama Tournament1936-1937 (Folder 9)
  - Norman Lear Productions (Wilde Oates and Beaux Stratagem)1977-1978 (Folder 10)
  - Pearce-Sunsites Lifestyle Improvement Project (Arizona)1981-1989 (Folder 11)
  - Pittsburgh Melody Tent1958-1959 (Folder 12)
  - Shimer College Summer Theater1939-1942 (Folder 13)
  - South Shore Music Circus1956-1958 (Folder 14)
  - University of California, Los Angles1980-1984 (Folder 15)
  - University of Southern California1985-1989 (Folder 16)
- Reference files (1947-1989), The reference files series is housed in 23 folders and is arranged alphabetically by the folder title provided by the creator. It contains information about different historical periods pertaining to manners, dress, and speech- presumably used to coach actors in period plays. Some period files also contain selected scenes from plays set within that historical period. This series also contains various notes and lectures on general theater and television topics, providing some insight to Carra's classroom style.
  - Bible Storiesundated (Folder 17)
  - Directing (approaches and controls)undated (Folder 18)
  - Directing courses, Lecture Outlines, Actingundated (Folder 19)
  - Eighteenth centuryundated (Folder 20)
  - Elizabethan and Stuartundated (Folder 21)
  - French Renaissanceundated (Folder 22)
  - Greek undated (Folder 23)
  - Lectures and Speeches1960-1989 (Folder 24)
  - Manual for Crew Heads (Carnegie Mellon University)undated (Folder 25)
  - Medievalundated (Folder 26)
  - Nineteenth century (first half)undated (Folder 27)
  - Nineteenth century (second half)undated (Folder 28)
  - Period Playsundated (Folder 29)
  - Pre-Elizabethan and Elizabethan undated (Folder 30)
  - Renaissanceundated (Folder 31)
  - Restorationundated (Folder 32)
  - Scene fundamentalsundated (Folder 33)
  - Shakespeare comedy scenesundated (Folder 34)
  - Shakespeare tragedy scenesundated (Folder 35)
  - Stagingundated (Folder 36)
  - "The Telephone" (script)1947 (Folder 37)
  - Television productionundated (Folder 38)
  - Twentieth century1978 (Folder 39)
- Stage productions (1931-1988), The stage production files account for the majority of the collection and cover 183 plays. These materials are housed in four boxes and arranged alphabetically by the title of the play. Following the title of the play, the location or group that performed the play is provided to assist researchers interested in particular groups or locations. For the most repeated locations or companies, an acronym has been assigned. The list of the acronyms and their meanings is provided above the container listing for this series. The amount of material in each folder varies widely but most include a playbill and newspaper articles. Other materials may include scripts, character charts, costume and set designs, correspondence, or other production notes. A typed script of Carra's thesis "The Great Magician" is included in folder 47.; CIT (Carnegie Institute of Technology- Pittsburgh, Penna.) CLO (Civic Light Opera- Pittsburgh, Penna.) CMU (Carnegie Mellon University- Pittsburgh, Penna.) FSC (Frances Shimer College- Waukegan, Ill.) GLSF (Great Lakes Shakespeare Festival- Lakewood, Ohio) IP (Interstate Players- Texas) MP (Mill Playhouse- Pleasant Mills, New Jersey) NWU (Northwestern University- Evanston, Ill.) SSMC (South Shore Music Circus- Boston, Mass.) UT (University of Texas- Austin, Texas)
  - "The Adding Machine" (CMU)1967-1968 (Folder 40)
  - "The Affected Young Ladies" (UT, FSC, CIT)1944-1955 (Folder 41)
  - "All's Well That Ends Well" (GLSF)1967 (Folder 42)
  - "Annie Get Your Gun" (CLO)1960 (Folder 43)
  - "Arms and the Man" (MP)1954 (Folder 44)
  - "Arsenic and Old Lace" (UT)1942 (Folder 45)
  - "As You Like It" (UT, CIT, GLSF)1944-1975 (Folder 46)
  - "Athens to Broadway" (NWU)1939 (Folder 47)
  - "Ball on a Rubber Chain" (or "Altruism")1937 (Folder 48)
  - "The Bartered Bride" (UT)1945 (Folder 49)
  - "Beaux Stratagem" (CMU, GLSF)1949-1968 (Folder 50)
  - "The Beggar's Opera" (GLSF, CMU)1972-1979 (Folder 51)
  - "Bell, Book, and Candle" (MP)1954 (Folder 52)
  - "Bells Are Ringing" (CLO, Tenthouse Music Theatre, Chicago)1959-1964 (Folder 53)
  - "La Boheme" (UT)1945 (Folder 1)
  - "Born King of the Jews" (Somerville County Theatre, Mass.)1931-1932 (Folder 2)
  - "Born Yesterday" (MP)1953 (Folder 3)
  - "Le Bourgeois Gentilhomme" (UT, GLSF)1942-1969 (Folder 4)
  - "The Boy Friend" (SSMC)1957 (Folder 5)
  - "Brigadoon" (SSMC, CLO)1957-1960 (Folder 6)
  - "The Cage" (CIT)1964 (Folder 7)
  - "Calamity Jane" (CLO)1961 (Folder 8)
  - "Can Can" (SSMC, CLO)1957-1962 (Folder 9)
  - "Candida" (GLSF, Longacre Theater, New York)1969-1970 (Folder 10)
  - "Candle Light" (MP)1953 (Folder 11)
  - "Cannibal Carnival" (Harvard Dramatic Club)1938 (Folder 12)
  - "Captain Carvallo" (MP)1953 (Folder 13)
  - "Carousel" (CLO)1963 (Folder 14)
  - "The Caucasian Chalk Circle" (CIT)1959 (Folder 15)
  - "Charm" (MP) 1953 (Folder 16)
  - "The Cherry Orchard" (UT, CIT, NWU, FSC)1944-1948 (Folder 17)
  - "The Chocolate Soldier" (Indiana University, CLO)1950-1961 (Folder 18)
  - "Clérambard" (CIT)1961 (Folder 19)
  - "The College Widow" or "Leave it to Jane" (CIT, Sheridan Square, New York)1946-1962 (Folder 20)
  - "Comedy" (Colonial Theater, Boston)1972 (Folder 21)
  - "Comedy of Errors" (GLSF)1974 (Folder 22)
  - "Cornor of God" (New Dramatists Committee)1953 (Folder 23)
  - "Cymbeline" (CIT, GLSF)1957-1968 (Folder 24)
  - "Cyrano de Bergerac" (GLSF)1967 (Folder 25)
  - "Damn Yankees" (SSMC, CLO)1958-1961 (Folder 26)
  - "Destry Rides Again" (CLO)1961 (Folder 27)
  - "La Dolce Vita" (Yale Experimental Theater)1937 (Folder 28)
  - "Don Juan" (MP, CIT)1954-1965 (Folder 29)
  - "The Dramatist" (CIT)1960 (Folder 30)
  - "An Evening Without Desdamona Fink"1962-1963 (Folder 31)
  - "Excursion" (CIT)1950 (Folder 32)
  - "Fanny" (SSMC, CLO)1958-1962 (Folder 33)
  - "Figaro's Marriage" (CIT)1961 (Folder 34)
  - "Finian's Rainbow" (SSMC)1956 (Folder 35)
  - "Firefly" (CLO)1963 (Folder 36)
  - "Flower Drum Song" (CLO)1962 (Folder 37)
  - "Follies" (CMU)1976 (Folder 38)
  - "The Fortune Teller" (San Antonio Civic Opera)1946 (Folder 39)
  - "The Frogs" (GLSF)1975 (Folder 40)
  - "George and Margaret" (MP)1953 (Folder 41)
  - "Getting Married" (Lenox Hill Playhouse)1952 (Folder 42)
  - "Glass Menagerie" (Theatre-on-the-Green, Fullerton, Calif.)1983 (Folder 43)
  - "The Good Women of Setzuan" (CIT)1949 (Folder 44)
  - "Le Grande Tour"1963 (Folder 45)
  - "The Great Campaign" (UT)1945 (Folder 46)
  - "The Great Magician"1937-1948 (Folder 47)
  - "Guys and Dolls" (SSMC, CLO, CMU)1958-1968 (Folder 48)
  - "Hamlet" (GLSF)1968 (Folder 49)
  - "Hansel and Gretel" (UT)1943-1944 (Folder 50)
  - "Happy Hunting" (SSMC)1958 (Folder 51)
  - "Hazel Kirke" (CIT)1948 (Folder 52)
  - "Hedda Gabler" (Rockport, Mass., and Providence, Rhode Island)1937-1938 (Folder 53)
  - "Henry IV" (NWU, GLSF)1939-1971 (Folder 54)
  - "Home is a Sacred Place" and "In the French Style" (California)1983 (Folder 55)
  - "How to Succeed in the Utility Business Without Really Trying"1964 (Folder 56)
  - "The Importance of Being Earnest" (GLSF)1966 (Folder 57)
  - "The Incredible Saga of Montmorency Clutchrider" (CMU)1973 (Folder 58)
  - "Irma La Douce" (White Barn Theatre)1963 (Folder 59)
  - "The Italian Straw Hat" (CIT, GLSF)1957-1973 (Folder 60)
  - "It's Up To You" (UT)1943 (Folder 1)
  - "The Jass Story"(Broadway)1958-1960 (Folder 2)
  - "Julius Caesar" (GLSF)1970 (Folder 3)
  - "Kind Lady" (FSC, IP)1941-1946 (Folder 4)
  - "The King and I" (SSMC, CLO)1956-1960 (Folder 5)
  - "King Lear" (GLSF)1966-1974 (Folder 6)
  - "Kismet" (SSMC, CLO)1956-1960 (Folder 7)
  - "Kiss Me Kate" (SSMC, CLO, CMU)1956-1977 (Folder 8)
  - "Knight of the Burning Pestle" (UT)1941 (Folder 9)
  - "Lady in the Dark" (SSMC)1957 (Folder 10)
  - "Lady Ride My Shoulder" (CIT)1950 (Folder 11)
  - "The Lady's at Work" (CIT Scotch and Soda Club)1948 (Folder 12)
  - "Land of the Free" (FSC)1940 (Folder 13)
  - "Lil'Abner" (CLO)1959 (Folder 14)
  - "Liliom" (CIT)1950 (Folder 15)
  - "Little Foxes" (MP)1953 (Folder 16)
  - "Little Women" (Rockport, Mass.)1937 (Folder 17)
  - "Lost in the Stars" (Indiana University)1950-1951 (Folder 18)
  - "Lysistrata" (Rockport, Mass.)1937 (Folder 19)
  - "Macbeth" (GLSF)1969 (Folder 20)
  - "Madness in Two Parts" (Hammonton, New Jersey)1956 (Folder 21)
  - "Madness on Bellevue Avenue" (Hammonton, New Jersey) undated (Folder 22)
  - "The Man Who Came to Dinner" (IP)1946 (Folder 23)
  - "Me and Juliet" (SSMC)1956 (Folder 24)
  - "Merchant of Venice" (CIT, GLSF)1967-1970 (Folder 25)
  - "The Merry Widow" (San Antonio Civic Opera, and CLO)1947-1963 (Folder 26)
  - "The Merry Wives of Windsor" (GLSF)1972 (Folder 27)
  - "A Midsummer Night's Dream" (GLSF, CMU)1973-1975 (Folder 28)
  - "Mikado" (San Antonio Civic Opera and Indiana University)1947-1951 (Folder 29)
  - "Misalliance" (GLSF)1967 (Folder 30)
  - Miscellaneous programs1940-1988 (Folder 31)
  - "La Moglie Ideale" (Yale Italian Society)1936 (Folder 32)
  - "The Most Happy Fella" (SSMC, CLO)1958-1959 (Folder 33)
  - "Mr. Lincoln, the President" 1981 (Folder 34)
  - "Music Man" (CLO)1963 (Folder 35)
  - "My Fair Lady" (Tenthouse Theatre, Chicago)1964 (Folder 36)
  - "My Maryland" (San Antonio Civic Opera)1944 (Folder 37)
  - "Naughty Marietta" (CLO)1959 (Folder 38)
  - "Oklahoma!" (CLO)1962 (Folder 39)
  - "One Warm Saturday" (CIT)1965 (Folder 40)
  - "Othello" (CIT, GLSF)1962-1971 (Folder 41)
  - "Our Town" (NWU, CMU, GLSF)1939-1975 (Folder 42)
  - "Pajama Game" (SSMC, CLO)1957-1960 (Folder 43)
  - "Pecos Bill"1957-1989 (Folder 44)
  - "The People, Yes" (UT)1941 (Folder 45)
  - "Pericles" (CMU)1971 (Folder 46)
  - "Physicians for Fools" (CIT)1962 (Folder 47)
  - "Picnic" (MP, CIT)1955-1958 (Folder 48)
  - "Pillars of Society" (CIT)1950 (Folder 49)
  - "Pipe Dream" (SSMC)1957 (Folder 50)
  - "Pittsburgh in Music" Music Festival1949 (Folder 51)
  - "Pittsburgh Sings" Music Festival1950 (Folder 52)
  - "Plain and Fancy" (SSMC)1956 (Folder 53)
  - "Playboy of the Western World" (GLSF)1974 (Folder 54)
  - "Post Road" (Rockport, Mass.)1937 (Folder 55)
  - "The Prince and the Piper" (UT, CIT)undated (Folder 56)
  - "Rhinoceros" (Playhouse, Pittsburgh)1966 (Folder 57)
  - "Richard III" (GLSF)1972 (Folder 58)
  - "Right You Are, If-" (UT, Wells College)1938-1945 (Folder 59)
  - "Rio Rita" (San Antonio Civic Opera)1944 (Folder 60)
  - "Rock n' Riot" (CIT Scotch and Soda Club)1947 (Folder 61)
  - "Romeo and Juliet" (GLSF, CMU)1967-1974 (Folder 62)
  - "Rosalinda" (CLO)1959 (Folder 63)
  - "Rose Marie" (CLO)1960 (Folder 64)
  - "Sally" (San Antonio Civic Opera)1947 (Folder 65)
  - "Say, Darling" (CLO)1959 (Folder 66)
  - "Irma La Douce" (White Barn Theatre)1966 (Folder 67)
  - Scout-O-Rama "On to Eagle"1951 (Folder 1)
  - "She Stoops to Conquer" (GLSF)1966 (Folder 2)
  - "Show Off" (MP)1953 (Folder 3)
  - "Silk Stockings" (SSMC)1957 (Folder 4)
  - "Situation Comedy" (CMU)1971 (Folder 5)
  - "The Skin of Our Teeth" (UT)1944 (Folder 6)
  - "South Pacific" (SSMC, CLO)1957-1960 (Folder 7)
  - "Squaring the Circle" (UT)1943 (Folder 8)
  - "Step into my Parlor" (MP)1954 (Folder 9)
  - "Stormy Weather"1953-1964 (Folder 10)
  - "A Streetcar Named Desire" (MP)1954 (Folder 11)
  - "Streets of New York" (FSC, MP)1941-1953 (Folder 12)
  - "The Student Prince" (CLO)1959 (Folder 13)
  - "A Sudden Spring" (SSMC and Ogunquit Playhouse, Maine)1956 (Folder 14)
  - "Summer and Smoke" (MP)1953 (Folder 15)
  - "Take Me Along" (CLO)1961 (Folder 16)
  - "Taming of the Shrew" (GLSF)1971 (Folder 17)
  - "Tartuffe" (GLSF)1973 (Folder 18)
  - "The Tempest" (CIT, GLSF)1953-1968 (Folder 19)
  - "The Texas Destiny" (IP)1946 (Folder 20)
  - "The Texas Round-up Revue and Ball" (UT)1945 (Folder 21)
  - "They Die for Peace" (UT)1943 (Folder 22)
  - "Thieves' Carnival" (Washington, D.C.)1953 (Folder 23)
  - "This is the Draft Board" (UT)1943 (Folder 24)
  - "Today Just Like Tomorrow" (CIT)1950 (Folder 25)
  - "Tonight at 8:30" (UT)1944 (Folder 26)
  - "Tosca" (UT)1944 (Folder 27)
  - "The Town Square" undated (Folder 28)
  - "Trial By Jury" (San Antonio Civic Opera)1947 (Folder 29)
  - "Tribal Warfare" (CMU)1981 (Folder 30)
  - "Troilus and Cressida" (GLSF, CMU)1968-1969 (Folder 31)
  - "Trouble in Tahiti" (MP)1955 (Folder 32)
  - "Twelfth Night" (UT, CIT, GLSF)1941-1973 (Folder 33)
  - "Two Dozen Roses" (MP)1954 (Folder 34)
  - "Under the Gaslight" (FSC, GLSF)1942-1974 (Folder 35)
  - "The Unsinkable Molly Brown" (CLO)1963 (Folder 36)
  - "Volpone" (CMU, GLSF)1970 (Folder 37)
  - "The Way of the World" (CMU)1972 (Folder 38)
  - "Where's Charley?" (SSMC)1958 (Folder 39)
  - "The Winter's Tale" (NWU, GLSF)1938-1966 (Folder 40)
  - "Wonderful Town" (CLO)1963 (Folder 41)
  - "You Can't Take It With You" (IP, Little Theatre, New Jersey, CIT)1946-1955 (Folder 42)
  - "You Never Can Tell" (GLSF)1971 (Folder 43)
- Television and Radio productions (1938-1983), The television and radio production files are housed in one box and arranged alphabetically by the title of the production. The materials in this series are similar to those in the stage productions series including scripts, newspaper articles, correspondence, and production notes. There are two folders worth of information about the Pulitzer Playhouse series in this series as well as a script for the television adaptation of Carra's own "The Great Magician." Some materials were more difficult to date than the stage production files due to the lack of a playbill or other dated material for a television production.
  - "Antony and Cleopatra"1983 (Folder 44)
  - "Arbie, the bug boy"undated (Folder 45)
  - "Black Death" undated (Folder 46)
  - Game Show ideasundated (Folder 47)
  - "Good Vibes"1981-1982 (Folder 48)
  - "The Great Magician"1938 (Folder 49)
  - Ideas1952-1980 (Folder 50)
  - "Live On Tape" (musical revue)1964 (Folder 51)
  - "The Matter of the Pots"1965-1967 (Folder 52)
  - "Pulitzer Prize Playhouse" (folder 1)1951-1952 (Folder 53)
  - "Pulitzer Prize Playhouse" (folder 2)1951-1952 (Folder 54)
  - "Stormy Weather"undated (Folder 55)
  - "The Tempest"1983 (Folder 56)
- Oversized materials (1946-1986), The oversized materials are housed in one folder in the second floor map case in drawer number eight. These materials are arranged following the order of the other materials in the collection and therefore subseries have been designated for project files, stage productions and television productions. Generally, these materials are architectural drawings and set designs. However, this series does include some advertising posters and oversized production notes.
  - Projects
    - Pearce-Sunsites Theater1986 (Folder 0)
    - Pittsburgh Music Tent1958-1959 (Folder 0)
  - Stage
    - "As You Like It"1965-1975 (Folder 0)
    - "Beggar's Opera"1979 (Folder 0)
    - "Can Can"1962 (Folder 0)
    - "Candida"1970 (Folder 0)
    - "Carousel"1963 (Folder 0)
    - "The Caucasian Chalk Circle"1959 (Folder 0)
    - "College Widow"/ "Leave It To Jane"1959-1962 (Folder 0)
    - "Comedy"1972 (Folder 0)
    - "Fanny"1962 (Folder 0)
    - "Firefly"1963 (Folder 0)
    - "Flower Drum Song"1962 (Folder 0)
    - "Glass Menagerie"1983 (Folder 0)
    - "Guys and Dolls"1958-1968 (Folder 0)
    - "Kind Lady"1946 (Folder 0)
    - "Kismet"1960 (Folder 0)
    - "Kiss Me Kate"1977 (Folder 0)
    - "Liliom"1950 (Folder 0)
    - "The Man Who Came To Dinner"1946 (Folder 0)
    - "Merry Widow"1963 (Folder 0)
    - "Merry Wives of Windsor"1972 (Folder 0)
    - "Molly Brown"c1962 (Folder 0)
    - "Music Man"1963 (Folder 0)
    - "Oklahoma!"1962 (Folder 0)
    - "One Warm Saturday"1965 (Folder 0)
    - "Othello"1962-1971 (Folder 0)
    - "Pittsburgh in Music"1949 (Folder 0)
    - "Pittsburgh Sings"1950 (Folder 0)
    - "Skin of Our Teeth"1946 (Folder 0)
    - "Summer and Smoke"1953 (Folder 0)
    - "Troilus and Cressida"1968 (Folder 0)
    - "As You Like It"1965-1975 (Folder 0)
    - "Way of the World"1972 (Folder 0)
    - "Wonderful Town"1963 (Folder 0)
    - "You Can't Take It With You"1946 (Folder 0)
    - "You Never Can Tell"1971 (Folder 0)
  - Television
    - "Pulitzer Prize Playhouse"1952 (Folder 0)
    - "The Tempest"1981 (Folder 0)